Game 01

Overview

Real World Date: 7/27/19

Game Date: 9/27/19 (Friday) -

TLDR

YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Gy-WpyQIYrQ&list=PLdNTLeOzaWPs8ftF4NXImYW7sEk7uzBVU&index=3&t=0s

Sorry, I don't have a TLDR for this one yet. I don't have time so you get the whole thing. If someone wants to write one, I will post it.

Game Notes

The sun is rising above the skyline in Seattle piercing through the slightly open blinds. A man lying in the bed is coming awake from the light. Looking around the room he remembers, this is not his house, and looking over at the lovely lady next to him he remembers why.

Through a time-lapse lends Trent is seen finding his pants and cloths, picks up something of hers and smiles, turning on the sink and filling up a cup of water, and kissing her on the head. Leaving the apartment and next to her bed is water and aspirin with a note that reads “to ease the hangover”.

While Trent is making his way down the road the scene shifts to follow a cab heading down the street. Inside the cab is a very bland looking man clutching a briefcase giving idle chatter to the talkative cabby. He gets to the bank, pulls on the doors, looks at the sign, and curses “Closed on weekends.”

The scene shifts back to some hotel where the same plan dressed man is tucking away stuff from the brief case into the bed, it is seen that the bed is ripped open and the last stack of bills is pulled from the case and stuffed into the mattress.

In the lobby the same man, Suni, is eating some food, reading the local newspaper, and glances up at the TV.

The news report stays the same, but the TV changes and we are in a bakery called Piroshki’s with employees and clientele speaking Russian. A black man orders something in Russian and gives a kind grin to the person behind the counter as he finds his seat. He looks up at the TV and listens to the announcer.

“Last night Judge Diana Tera died in her sleep, investigators are pointing towards foul play, but with few leads.” The screen shows a house with yellow tap and officers doing their job. The new caster continues “Sources say she died in her sleep through suffocation. She was fairly well known in the community as an avid dog lover. Seattle Seabarks was her community project and she will be sorely missed.”

(In Russian) “Yeah, by rich folks who tend to pay off the antics of their children.” Sasha didn’t even notice the woman from behind the counter came around to hand him is pastry.

“Da, I have heard she has let many people who were clearly guilty off with a light sentence.” Sasha replies (also in Russian).

The characters can be seen doing various tasks throughout the day. Xenori has music blaring in her headphones as she is working on a motorcycle. She can be seen nodding her head and tapping her foot. While she is working on some computer tech in this very suffocated bike. “Status?” the bike revs, “cool!” she says looking up at something that only she can see in her glasses.

Her helmet comes crawling over to her on the back of what looks like tiny little bugs on the ground. Once it taps her boot, she picks it up and the bugs disperse.

Outside of the building she comes tearing out around the corner between cars not even looking. She accelerates and heads into the city. She blows by a park where Suni can be seen walking down looking at the trees. He flips open his phone makes a call and looks out among the trees.

A man dressed for a date, holds open the door for a lovely lady dressed as if she is going out on the town. He takes a peak at his phone and sees a number he knows but doesn’t keep. “I don’t have time for him now.”

Looking over the city scape Vic and his date, Susan, enjoy a meal at the Nest. During dinner Susan starts taking about rare artifacts from ancient Egypt. She talks about her job is to track them down at all cost. She then shyly admits “This is how I first came across you. But then I meet you and forgot to ask you to help me track something down, and then I kept meeting with you at the gym and asking you by then kind of got awkward, but now I need to get results.”

“Ancient Egyptian Items are kind of outside my forte.” Vic suggests

“I know where the item is, I know who has it, they won’t part with it, we know because we offered them 300k. I was told you have skills in this area and … look if you’re not able to do it, it is fine. I am sorry, I probably shouldn’t have brought this up.” Susan says rushing to end the conversation and looking a little embarrassed.

“now wait… what is it and who has it. I can take a look.”  Vic assures her.

“It is a diadem…” she says “… it was worn by female warriors from ancient Egypt when buried with their queens to protect them from after death. One ended up in Seattle and it is at a pawn shop in the Central District.”

Vic tells her he will look into it and see what he can do. He receives a notification letting him know traffic and time estimate for getting to the Fox Theater.

As Vic is exiting his car passing the valet his keys, he hears the rev of a motorcycle pass by. He looks up and the scene begins to follow the lady on the bike.

The bike comes to a stop under the lights of the nightclub Kremwerk. Inside the music is pumping and the energy is hot. The floor is crowded the place is full of great energy. Xen looks around the room and briefly sees someone she recognizes, but it is impossible.

Xenori recognizes him from another world called the Digital Web. But as he passes by someone, she loses him in the crowd. She quickly taps her wrist and pulls on her rings. The bugs from before shoot out of her jacket and scatter, when they clutter they can be scene, but when they scatter, they are inconspicuous and hard to make out from the background.

She throws on her glasses and starts to dance again. Buzzing around the room trying to find him she is weaving in and out of people, but he is nowhere to be found. A cluster of bugs centers on an anomaly. She flips her viewing over to that as a few can be seen returning to her. She sees white spots in the room. They do not seem to be detectable though human eyes, but they are there. These are also known as fragments or pieces of whiteouts left behind. These are spots only known in the digital web. Looking around the room, no one notices them, and they do not seem to affect anything. After 30 minutes or so, they are gone.

“Blue and white strips” Trent thought. Looking around at the scene being lit up by the flashing lights of police, firefighters, and ambulance vehicles. “I heard something that sounded like a flag on a really windy day.” A police officer kneeling in front of him patiently waiting for Trent to collect his thoughts. She looks at him, blood on his face and cloths. The officer has seen people in shock.

“Whenever you’re ready” she encourages him.

“I was heading to the club, I decided to walk because it wasn’t a bad night, and the club is not too far. I picked up something to drink and was just thinking about how the rest of my night was going to go. That is when I heard something…”

“Screaming?” the officer asks.

“No…” Trent tries to remember what he heard. “I could hear this flapping noise, like the wind hitting his cloths. He didn’t make any other sounds. I… I just dove out of the way. I guess I wasn’t really thinking what was happening.”

“It’s ok.” The officer attempts to comfort Trent “You had no idea, you had to react. This isn’t something you could have prevented, and honestly if you tried, you may not be alive to tell us the story. So, the victim hit the ground next to you…”

“Yeah,” Trent tries to stick to what he remembers without trying to remember what he saw. “He just smashed into the ground.”

She continues to ask him some additional questions before asking him “Do you need a ride home?”

“I am just around the corner, thank you.” Trent replies. Trent wonders off and heads home for the night. As he makes his way down the street a tall man can be seen standing in front of Trinity Nightclub checking IDs.

There is a line to get in and Sasha is checking IDs and talking to the patrons before they enter the venue. At times there is needed to be two people, but mostly Sasha can handle it on his own. There is always a lull of the night where nothing happens for 10 minutes or so. It is always the longest 10 minutes waiting for the next person. It gives time for people to drift into their thoughts.

“Hello?” a very attractive lady in a teal dress stands in front of Sasha trying to get his attention.

Sasha realizes he must have been in a daydream or something and apologizes and checks the ladies ID. “Jillian, 23, picture matches mostly, she is probably legit” he thinks to himself, and hands her back the ID and lets her in. He checks his watch… “an hour? How in the… where is Bobbie?” Bobbie was supposed to relieve him 15 minutes ago.

When he opens the door to see what is going on he sees Jillian walking around checking her phone, but everyone else is frozen. Standing real still and not moving. He hangs a sign on the front doors, for people to form a line and moves in.

Sasha can feel a burst of energy pulsing through the room. He opens up his sight, it is a magickal sense that allows him to see the chi that everyone gives off and he finds something wrong. The chi you see from people usually pulses with life, but everyone’s was in a state of vibration. It was almost as if they were asleep. In the middle of the dance floor he sees a kid, Bernard (poor kid), he remembers giving him Xs on his hands because he was only 18. He couldn’t see any flow of chi.

As he makes his way through the crowd and bumps or nudges people they start coming back “to life”. They act as though nothing happened. Pick right back up with the music and keep partying. Bernard, on the other hand, didn’t. He fell over on touch from Sasha. He was dead.

The police came and took the body, they asked a few questions, but ruled it as a possible drug overdose.

A couple days pass, and we see the city change. Fog comes into the city; the streets change form party goers and tourist to business women and men and parents getting their children on the bus. The traffic changes, it gets lighter as the Ubers and Lifts are no longer transporting drunks and instead the upper-class Ubers and Lifts are transporting business individuals. The buses are on schedule and people are going in and coming out of the tunnels from the train.

Suni is heading towards the tunnels when he feels a measure of what can be described as wrongness. It hits him in the pit of his stomach, and it sends him for a wild ride. It feels like he was drugged or beat up. Images blur, sounds reverberate, everything has a horrible smell, and he has a difficult time regaining control. He looks up and sees a school bus pulling away from its stop. Once it pulls away, he can feel the darkness leaving with it. This is a sense of a problem with the spinning wheel. As a Euthanatoi he has never felt this imbalance so strongly before and has no idea where it came from except something to do with that bus and/or maybe the people on it?... He isn’t sure. Suni continues to head down into the train station and boards a train.

The train goes all around Seattle. When it leaves downtown district, it changes from underground tunnel transportation to above ground. In some districts it goes above the roads, so it doesn’t have to stop. Other Districts it can be seen ridding in the median alongside traffic, and it even stops at some red lights. Central District the Link Light Rail moves down the median. A woman gets out at one of the designated stops and jumps on a bus. She gets out along this tight road near a single car garage shop.

Vic walks out and holds the door open for her and makes his way down the street. He arrives at the pawn shop Capitol Palace. It is a purple building with some graffiti tags on the side. The front parking lot has a chain link fence wrapped around it with barbed wire on top. Outside in the warm weather sits a larger black gentleman with a coat. Vic suspects there is a gun under there.  Vic did a little homework before coming.

The diadem is possibly a fake, the legendary items are said to be a myth, but in a world of magick anything can be real. He also knows the pawn shop is ran by a local gang called Duces 8.

Duces 8 is known publicly because one of their young members was murdered by a cop. He was walking down the street rapping along with some band he was listening to through his headset. A cop pulled up behind him and yelled something. He could see the 2-8 Tattoo on the back of the kids’ neck.

Duces 8 is lesser known for their protection in the Central District. Cops respond when they got time, and this will allow things to happen to people. This group offers protection for the people who the cops can’t protect (or flat out just don’t want to). Don’t get this wrong, this isn’t a group of heroes. They are murders, thieves, and more. If you don’t pay up for protection, you will somehow. They have no problem letting thieves know which places are not under their protection (for a fee). They also deal a little in drugs and guns, but that is a very small part of their operation.

The Kid’s name was Kev, when he turned around, he pulled out his phone to pause the music and the officer shot him 6 times. He was super afraid of a 155lb black kid heading home from school. Reports were not clear on if the kid really did pull out his phone, and one witness said that the officer didn’t even say anything before pulling the trigger. That witness has left town or something. The officer? Still works the beat after a small vacation.

Capitol Palace is your typical poor city pawn shop. There are some good items in there, but they probably trade with other pawn shops to keep the really expensive stuff out of there. It is also a good way for a small shop like this to turn a quick profit. A man behind the counter goes by the name of De nods at Vic when he comes in. Vic doesn’t look like he is from Central, but whatever. De stands out. He looks like he has been through some shit, but what looks awkward on him is he is wearing the diadem. It like of looks like the descriptions Vic read up on.

Vic starts a conversation with De about the Diadem. De doesn’t let him touch it but engages the conversation. He tells Vic that he is waiting on someone to come tell him what he has. He knows it is worth a lot because how quick someone came in to offer him a couple hundred thousand. De is quick to paranoia when Vic quotes $300,000 but is eased back into the conversation when Vic buys some stuff. Vic tries a couple times to get him to accept an offer, but De isn’t having it. Vic thanks him and hands him a card and tells him if he changes his mind, to give him a call.

Back in Downtown Trent wakes up from a night of being messed up. He still has images in his head of the guy falling from the building. He keeps hearing the splat as the body crumbles to the ground. Trent gets up drinks something, throws up, and makes his way around town. Trent starts walking the Seattle streets and parks. He pauses to let a blue bus pass in front of him.

The Bus is heading north towards the Cascade District. It is about 2 minutes from its next stop. Taking a look from about a couple blocks away, Sasha can be seen running towards the stop. Sounds of controlled breathing can be heard by people Sasha is passing. He is jumping over Seattle Times stands and running along concrete squares that hold soil for the trees and plants along the city streets. He flips off the last one, steps, rolls and continues running. Crossing the street, he realizes he made a mistake, he didn’t expect the car to run the light. He jumps and using his left hand, pushes off the hood of the orange car. He lands backwards on the street, rolls, and continues.

The bus is closing its doors when a hand goes inside and reopens to Sasha apologizing asking, “is this bus going to Queen Anne Hill?” The Driver nods. “In front of Mary’s Place?” She nods again, and he gets on board.

Around the corner Xenori is heading south towards the West End Bridge. Sleepers can’t see this, but around the bike are tiny little bots keeping a look out. They fly ahead to see traffic patterns and report back so Xenori has little to nothing to worry about. On the second seat is a hot meal tied down. She hasn’t seen Lucas in a while, and he would probably be appreciative of this.

Xen gets to the bridge and the sounds of the city die away. It isn’t as busy here. The thuds of cars going across the bridge can he heard. Lucas talks to her for a while. He tells her about the stabbings. Three so far this week to homeless youth. Cops have come, but they are just here to take the bodies away. They don’t plan on doing anything.

Xenori looks off in the distance and her nanos react. They map out the area and find a good advantage point for her to install some cameras. The scene changes and she can be seen assembling the cameras and the bots help her install them for best viewability.

“You dropped this.” Trent says to a person in the park. He looks at Trent and his bright red large spiky hair, and then looks at the wallet where he can see a 100 slightly hanging out, “it’s cool. Take it.” Trent encourages as the man takes the wallet and goes. Trent reaches into his back pocket and pulls out another wallet. He pauses for a second and gives a little shake of the head trying to live in the now and not revisit last night. “Fuck! I know nothing about that kid. Why did that even happen?” a lady is looking at him kind of weird, hands him a 5, and turns and walks away. Trent looks around and sees his reflection in a trashcan. He doesn’t look good today.

(Yes, I changed the day, sorry) Later that afternoon, Vic returns the Central District with a fancy looking briefcase. He nods to the guard out front and walks into the store. De can be heard talking to himself when he enters.

“I want to make you an offer on the Diadem.” Vic initiates with De.

“The Diadem belongs to us.” De says

“Us?” Vic questions, “Look, in this case there is 500k. It is yours for the diadem.”

“Your offer has been accepted. We appreciate your generosity. You can leave us the briefcase and go.” De says in a very monotone.

Vic takes a split second and then starts throwing up his wards and shielding his mind. De just hit him with a psychic attack and it was a good one. A mundane person would have left the briefcase and went about their day, but luckily Vic has training.

“Ok…” Vic says “De, I see what you’re doing. I am here to make a business transaction with you and I am not leaving until I get what I want.” Vic says.

“But you are leaving us, you will also leave the money, you will leave your weapon, you will leave and forget you ever were here. We see that Susan sent you, and we will pay her a visit too. We will remove everything you ever had and cared about. You belong to us. Now, our puppet, pull your weapon, and end this nightmare.”

Vic pulls his gun and without thinking he fires the gun at Dee. He places his shot dead center of his head, “shit.”

Outside the guard hears the gun shoot and looks in the window to see De falling over from being blasted at point blank range. He pulls his gun and opens fire. It is an automatic weapon of some kind. It is just unloading into the place.

Vic drops, grabs the diadem, picks back up the briefcase, and gets the hell out of there. On his way out he tags the gas main with a sticker, but as he starts to move again gets shot in the arm. He smashes into the wall “FUCK!” he curses as he runs out the back door.

Vic drops the ground draws a circle, dabs a little power into the filed, and adds a match for fire. When he strikes the match, the gas explodes, and the gunfire stops. Vic runs and can hear sirens not too far away. He turns towards Tito’s Garage but before he gets there runs into Suni. “Come on, this way.”

Suni helps Vic hide the diadem and they get back to Vic’s house to clean up. Vic gives Susan a call, but it goes to voicemail.

The next day there is a news report about a gang dispute in the Central District that authorities are looking into. Xenori is watching this through her glasses. She is traveling a lite version of the digital web looking for Technocracy traffic.

A routine signals her and she opens the window. It is an IP she is very familiar with. A lot of Technocrats used this channel back in the day and it looks like some still use it now. The contact was made with someone that is saying at apartments that are nearby. They are speaking about some kind of diadem. It is mostly in code so unless Xen knows the specifics it is hard to make out.

She starts trying to track any other traffic about a diadem or any head piece and nothing is coming up. If no one else is talking about it, it must be big. She decides to go check it out. Xenori starts tapping into people’s wifi trying to find which room it was that had contact. She discovers it and goes on sound recon. The person is in their apartment watching TV. Xen can hear the laugh track form some sitcom.

Her bots alert her to familiar identity across the street. Trent is walking up, looking like he had very little sleep, and he goes to enter the apartment building as a female officer was exiting the building.

“Hey, Trent right?” she says, “What are you doing here?”

“I, and just… “ Trent begins but gets interrupted with paramedics come moving out of the building with an elderly female on the stretcher being rolled out. She is on oxygen and they are bringing her to the ambulance. “Ok, you here for her?”

“Yeah, I was in the area and there was a 911 call, but what’s up?” she asks

“I am trying to find out anything about him.” Trent says.

The officer nods with that knowing look. “His name was Manel Devine, this isn’t your fault there was nothing you could have done, anyone could have done. Forensic says it looks like he slipped and flipped over his balcony railing. Sorry I got to run, you should see someone, but this isn’t on you.” She says as she heads out to the street.

Trent tries to listen in on what they are talking about and all he hears is the word suffocation.

Xenori looks up Mandel, his floor was right above the person she was looking into, who was… right above the floor of the old lady they are wheeling out…

Xenori sends in her bots into the room they zoom around looking for anyone, and they find a woman on the floor, holding her throat as if she was choking, reaching for her dropped phone. The screen is lit from an incoming call with the name Vic Black on it.

Prev | Home | 01 Game Notes | Game 05

Game 03

Overview

Real World Date: 09/07/19

Game Notes

Xenori takes a moment to orientate, it wasn’t the first time something like this has happened to her. She reaches out and grabs the counter and starts to make her way toward the door. Trent appeared in front of her and placed his hands on her shoulders. “Look, sorry. I thought you were just being rude, but now I see something is wrong. Let me help.”

Xenori shook her head in reassurance, “No, it is better that I…” she trails off as her vision starts to return. She can see a smoky room, and some figure off in the distance. Xen reaches out with her senses and can tell she is not seeing in the apartment, it is somewhere else. “Maybe I should sit down…”

Trent thinks this is a good idea and brings her to the living room. He sets her on the couch, gets her a pillow, an empty garbage can, and some water. He is not sure what is happening but wants to be prepared for the worse. Just a few days ago a man almost fell on him from a 5 th story window, and now a techno-mage is having some kind of backlash in his living room.

Vic is sitting in the lobby of the Vet Hospital killing some time while his new friend Suni is back on a metal table that isn’t quite his size getting stitched up. Suni passed out, Vic know this because he can hear him snoring. Vic notices a new game on his phone, must be a type of bloatware companies install. Play a little bit, get addicted, and then they temp you to pay a little to get more power. Tellus Electronics (A Pentex Company) puts out an app a month like this. Ever heard of Quazy Cups?

He opens up the game and starts playing. It is a little on the nose. The first splash screen is for the new Warlock: the Pretension supplement by Black Dog Game Factory, then it moves on to the load screen. It is a game called Battle WiXards. “Why are people always trying to replace a Z with an X.” Vic says as he begins playing. It is a pretty simple game, you open into an arena, another mage appears, you need to take them down in this turn base style competition. Vic plays a couple rounds and then loads the next level.

He starts off big, “FIREBALL!!!!” Vic screams as his character (whoa talking about meta) has the text bubble popup above his head reading the same thing.

Xenori sees the figure turn, wave a wand, and then some text bubble pops above his head reading “FIREBALL!!!!” (because three exclamation points isn’t enough). She dives out of the way, but gets singed by this 8-bit red, orange, and yellow sprite flying across the screen. She can hear this low-res midi file begin playing.

“Shit! I am in the DW, but where?” Xenori asks.

“The DW?” Trent replies

“Sorry, hold on.” Xen tells him as she begins to focus. She swings her hands, but it is not quite working. After taking a quick look at the code she groans, “LIGHTNING STRIKE!!!” she hollers out and it blast back at the shadowy mage. (ST Note: Sorry, I really meant for this to be part of the game, but I forgot. So I decided to put it in here instead.)

Their fight goes on like this for a round or two as Xenori is tapping into the core code of this application. It is her code! This is her style, commenting (probably none), class groupings, architect, and even the define names are to her standards. ‘WTF’ she says to herself as she jumps out of the way of another Fire Blast. ‘I never wrote anything like this.’ She thinks, but then finds a file paradox.ini. She starts tapping her fingers and her BUGs bring her rings out and lines them up with her fingers. She gives additional controls to her character.

“What the hell is going on?” Trent asks as the BUGs fly towards him and start forming into some kind of shape. “Fuck… me….” He says as they fly onto his face and start forming some kind of light in his eyes.

Xenori jumps over a lightning blast and then looks up. She can see through the glass to the user. It is like looking out of a big window to a really big person tapping away at some video game.

The moment Xen looks directly at Vic he tucks his head back and starts poke! Poke! Poke! Poking! the screen. Xen tucks her head down and puts her arms up to stop the force vibrations coming from the touch sensitivity of the phone. It is hitting her in the head repeatedly.

Trent appears in the game and is looking around a bit confused. Vic gets surprised “Two of you? Oh you have not seen the power of this WiXard!”

They continue fighting Trent figuring out the game with a little bit of Xenori ’s instructions. She points up and he can see Vic in some kind of room. Xenori programs in

Messagebox(“Were you at all involved in Susan ’s Murder?”,”Incoming Message”,messageBoxOptions.YesNo)

The message pops up on Vic ’s screen “Holy Shit, I’ve been hacked.” He raises the phone to smash it to the ground when another message pops.

Messagebox(“I know who did this to her.”,”Wait!”,messageBoxOptions.Ok,messageboxIcon.Warning)

Vic sees this right before he throws, pauses, then shuts off the phone and pulls the sim chip. Trent and Xenori wake up in his living room. “Ummmm, what?” Trent says with elegance if a monkey at a formal dinner.

“So, this place is about 5 hectares?” Sasha ask a man sitting on a bench in a park. Seeing the confusion on his face, Sasha squints and then says, “about 10 or so acres.”

“Oh”, the maintenance man says. “yeah, Lake Union Park is about 12 acres named after the fresh water lake and shipping canal. Out there are some historic ships I would suggest stopping and taking a look at, the Lady Washington plays movies on the boat, you can climb aboard and watch for free. The Museum of History and Industry, or MOHAI , is also really neat to check out.”

Sasha kindly listens to the man as he goes through his spiel. He tightens up his laces and begins to jog around the park looking for good spots to practice his parkour workout. By the time he was done the sun had set and a light show begun at the MOHAI center.

Sasha stops at the large fountain, well, it is more of a pond, but it is raised up like it should be a fountain. There isn’t any water works in the middle or at least any above water level. It is lit up at night and shines very bright. The pond is called the Model Boat Pond. Daily people are drawn to the pond to test their model boats. Some weekends it could get really crowded. There is some kind of minor current in the pond. Touching the water idly Sasha reaches out with his Chi and senses the water calling him. “Place in me your creation and I will test it.”

Looking around the park he can’t find anything he could use as a boat, but Sasha is a master of life. He goes to a tree that producing purple and white flowers and plucks one off with some leaves. He concentrates with his life energies he built up from his workout and it reforms into a water lily . Placing it into the pond the current pulls it out around the middle and brings it back to him. Reaching into the water he can see this glow around the lily and on touching it he can feel energy come from the pond into him. “This is a Node.”

In the park most of the crowd is over watching the light show on the south side of the MOHAI . Sitting on a park bench are two large men. The bench is positioned to allow them to bend in unnoticed by passersby and they tend not to make too much noise. They have been watching Sasha . When he retrieves the lily from the water, one taps the other and points over to him. “See that?”

“See them?” the other notices a group of others quickly making their way to the pond.

Sasha turns to go and sees a man standing in front of him. This man has others alongside him and they look and feel threatening. They are standing real still, their breath, though there, is light. Their appearance looks like drug addicts high on uppers that could make one violent. “Good evening fellas. I was just going that way.” He says and starts to move. The creature in front of him hisses and his face changes into a monstrous creature.

“What the fuck is that!” Sasha yells out and starts to make his way away from them, but quickly notices others have already come up on his flank. One of the men looks very old. He is wearing a top hat. He lets out a screech and his mouth drops down to his belly.

The creatures he first encountered starts running up towards him. Two of them jump in the pond and continue running. These creatures are strong, the water slows them, but only by a little. The water is parting behind them from the sheer force of their momentum. Sasha needs to get all of them on one side of him.

Sasha summons his chi and runs towards the pond he is going to kick off the side of it and leap to the other side. It is a feat beyond human compacity, but not when mystical energies are at play. Sasha jumps like he has done 100 times, but reality had different plans. In the air an explosion of force hits Sasha and he tumbles back down and lands in the middle of the pond.

The creatures stop and turn around. The water hits the edge of the pond and splashes up about 6 feet or so. Sasha tries to run, but one grabs him and throws him. Sasha flies out of the pond about 20 feet or so and breaks his fall with an elegant roll, and some force resistance against the ground. He uses that force to push him to run away. Sasha sees the MOHAI and thinks maybe he can stand a chance if he could come at them one on one.

At this time others in the park have taken notice and have started running towards the parking lot. From the parking lot some of the pedestrians split off as a sports car comes zooming in and onto the green.

The scene switches to a person playing doctor with a grown ass man on his K9 metal surgery bed snoring. Suni wakes up to a sound of a rattle. He looks around and is walking towards school. Suni knows where he needs to go and is holding books that read, ‘History’? ‘Social Arts’?, he can’t worry about that right now, he will sort out his books when he gets to class.

As he is approaching the building the main entrance is a 3-story building with the name of the school on the front “Highlands”, but then something flashes in the world kind of like a glitch. Colors of green, purple, blue flash across the sky like an old TV set is going bad. The school sign changes to “Lowlands” and then back again. The building also shrinks to one story, and then reappears to 3 stories.

He is sitting in the classroom but doesn’t quite remember how he got here. He was just outside, but he isn’t worried about suddenly appearing in the classroom. What he is worried about is being an old man in grade school. He gets nervous and reaches for his books to get out of there and sees his hands are that of a child’s hands. On some level Suni knows he is in a lesson from Coyote, but right here and now, that isn’t a thought on his mind. He is a kid in school, he is supposed to be there, and he must pay attention.

“Suni? What do you think?” the teacher calls on him.

Suni, clearly wasn’t paying attention he tries to give a non-answer “Like it says in the book, that was everyone’s opinion.” Which was probably not the best of answers. The teacher looks mortified and behind her on the board he thinks he reads the word ‘Holocaust’. Other students start to laugh at him as what tends to happen in childhood dreams, but Sani is a shaman he has walked in dreams before and he knows how to control his state and observe so whatever lesion is being taught he will absorb.

Sitting in the classroom is a pretty little girl. She has the book, but it isn’t open. The whole time she is staring straight at the board. She isn’t moving, she is blinking and breathing, but she is sitting as still as one can. Everyone in class ignores her, they talk around her like she is not there, they don’t bother passing a note to her just toss it past. It is like she doesn’t exist. When going around the room reading, she is skipped over, and it doesn’t seem like it is on purpose. No one notices her except for Sani . It is like he is the first person to see her in a long time.

She looks over at him and SCREAMS.

Sani wakes up asking for a phonebook. The doctor thinking he is totally delirious tell him, “it is 2019, lay down before you pop a stitch.” Vic comes in as the doctor is finishing up.

“Do you have a phone book?” Sani asks as Vic stares at him, then looks up at the vet who shrugs.

“What do you need?” Vic asks.

“Is there a school called Highlands?”

“There used to be I am pretty sure.” Vic remembers a news article from a couple years back where the community was in uproar because they changed the name of the school from Highlands to something. He sees Teddy the Vet’s phone on the counter and opens the browser. Typing in a few characters he finds the school, “Lawton.”

“We need to go. Now.” Sani says as the vet cut the last thread and slapped a bandage on him.

Xenori and Trent are sitting in the living room and she is attempting to catch Trent up on what has been going on over the last few days.

“So, who was that?” Trent asks.

“That was Vic , he was in a relationship with Susan, girl on the 4 th floor of Harbor Steps . I was at her apartment when the Terminator attacked me.” She explains.

“Is that how you travel? Did you teleport through my phone?” Trent asks

“Yeah.” It wasn’t but to explain the complication of how she just used the GPS in his phone to figure out where he was at and using the hardlines of the Apartment to secure a safer travel would have probably taken this conversation down a nerdy route.

That didn’t stop the conversation from going down a nerdy route. Trent doesn’t get to talk to too many people about how his teleportation works. He talks about shadow travel and how he can manipulate the space between the light and the shadow like a curtain that if he can connect two points, he can step in one and out another anywhere. He then takes her to his setup room where he has things stacked in a particular manner with shaped light so he can reach in the room at any moment form his coat pocket. He also pulls out his weapon of choice, a giant mallet.

Xenori tells Trent about the Digital Web . “it is less of the internet as you are describing and more of a reality of its own. You have heard of multiple dimensions, right?” Trent acknowledges that he has, but not quite sure he believes in them. “Well this world is a place we can physically go to or perceive. There is a whole ‘nother world in there and it is hard to really describe its limitations. You kind of need to experience to grasp it. I have spent years in there and I still haven’t tapped all the reality it offers.”

“So… Susan , you said her name was?” Trent asks and Xen nods. “What does she have to do with anything? Do you think Vic did something?”

“No, I don’t think so. I have worked with him before, but he doesn’t quite know who I am.” She says. “I don’t know why they murdered her or what she even has to do with the Technocracy , but I think it is best we find out. Especially with that Terminator attacking us on sight.”

Sani and Vic are stuck in traffic. It has been a nightmare. Seattle traffic isn’t the worst in the world ( that award goes to the Paradox Backlash that invented Atlanta ), but when it gets bad, everything gets bad. Most people in Seattle rely on public transportation. Seattle Public Transportation is actually really good. The Link Light Rail gets you quickly to the different districts and the bus systems have lanes that allow them to avoid traffic. Sani and Vic have gotten off on their third road to try and get around this traffic. They have spent an hour into the night trying to get there.

Sani is just sitting there unphased by any of this. He knows he will arrive exactly when he is supposed to. Vic on the other hand is losing his mind with all this traffic. They pull up to a red light and Vic sees a man being chased by a hoard of monsters. “I think I know that guy.”

Sani looks over where Vic is staring. “Should we help?”

Without answering Vic took his car to the limits. The tires squeal as the car rights itself and cuts through the parking lot, onto the grass, and drifts to finally grip onto the side walk. People are splitting out of the way as Vic sets his car to use it like a ram if need be. As they pass two stoned out dudes, pointing at the action thinking it is some kind of movie, Vic and Sani do not see those two get yanked out of the way by two large beasts.

“What are those things?” Sani asks

“I am not sure, but they ain’t human.” Vic says as they come to a stop out front of the MOHAI and jump out to chase after the monsters that just went inside.

Trent starts connecting the dots that Mandel was on the 5 th floor, Susan was on the 4 th , and that lady being wheeled out for shortness of breath, she was on the 3 rd floor. “Yeah, right on top of each other.” Xenori said.

“Well, we need to go back there and see if we can find anything.” Trent says as he stands up and grabs his things. “You Readdd…” Trent starts to speak but his living room light flickered, and he stumbled into a shadow. He fell and reached out to grab something, but only grabbed a BUG and with Xenori ’s connection to the device almost pulled her in too.

Xen concentrates and sees her device falling through a wormhole of some sort but can’t place its locality.

When Trent sees the opening back into the real world, he is surprised to see that he is falling towards the tail of an airplane.

Museum of History & Industry ( MOHAI ) is the largest private heritage organization in Washington state, maintaining a collection of nearly 4 million artifacts, photographs, and archival materials that primarily focus on Seattle and the greater Puget Sound region. It is a sight that people who are local to the area should see. Preferably not being chased after by some drug addicted monsters and maybe during operating hours.

Sasha smashed open the glass door and made his way inside. The entrance comes in on the second floor, and Sasha runs to the left. In the middle of this Museum there is an old Boeing B-1 on display. Someone with good athleticism could jump from the railing to the wing of the plane.

Sasha Jumps, grabs on to one of the cables suspending the plane, swings around, and kicks one of the monsters in the face. He continues to swing and runs up the top wing towards the middle. Two creatures make the same jump and land on the wing and begin to run up on all fours towards Sasha .

The rest of the monsters are on the walk way, trying to figure out how to get to the plane without taking everything down. They are dead focused on Sasha , that they do not see Vic and Sani come up from behind them.

Vic draws a circle and creates a small pop as he concentrates on his spell. He makes a little fire form in front of him and he mumbles the right words to cause the fire to grow. Sani starts doing a chant and says “I got them where I want them.”

Everyone hears a bolt shake out of the overhang walkway, but nothing happens. “Well…” Sani mused, “That was unexpected.”

The monsters leaps at Sasha , he catches the first one by the shoulders to prevent him moving in to bite him and uses the momentum to flip up and over the second leaping monster. Sasha grabs a support cable and they slide back down to the plane. The first monster’s nails start digging into Sasha ’s skin.

The plane gives a huge jolt as everyone grabs onto something to maintain balance. Trent lands on the back of the plane and grabs onto the tail. “Red head?” Sasha says, “What are you doing here?”

Did you know that you always can see your nose? Go ahead, close one eye and look forward, it is there. It is in the way, but you don’t think about it. This is because your mind decides what is important at the time and seeing your huge nose in the way all the time is not important. There is so much you are seeing, hearing, smelling, feeling, and tasting right now, that your mind is defending you and holding back that info. Imagine if you could set your own limits. Trent has figured this out. It is almost as if time has stopped and he takes a look around.

Trent steps off the plane and walks in the air over to where the monsters are on the ledge and sees Vic and Sani . He comes back over to see what Sasha is handling. He also notices the room has a lot of shadows “I will keep that in mind for later”. Trent allows all that to process as the world returns to normal and he is hanging on to the tail. From his sleeve a tiny drone comes flying out and starts inspecting the room.

Sani shakes his rattler and hums again, seeing the commotion he knows that just a little more vibration can cause that suspended rotary motor in the glass case will come loose. He knows this, he feels it, and Coyote willing, it is real. And with enough belief, it is. The motor snaps from its support and slides down, crashes through the glass, and throws a monster down to the first floor.

Sasha and the creature continue fighting. The monster is tough, and this is a new experience for Sasha . It can withstand his blows and he quickly realizes he isn’t doing much harm to it. More creatures make it onto the wing, the plane shakes and swings which makes balancing difficult, but everyone manages to hang on.

Xen sees an opportunity. There is a change in Force and Mass to the plane and she opens her IDE. She taps in some code that the drone should be able to apply to the consensual reality class that is running in the museum. By slightly tweaking the mass and applied forces she could tell the plan to dip. The drone loaded her class file and it worked like a charm, the plane swung, and the right wing spun up. A Ghoul fell everyone else seemed to hang on.

The creatures on the ledge turn to Sasha and Vic , Vic breaks his circle and releases the large ball of fire and blast two of them into oblivion.

Xen, back at Trent ’s apartment, calls her BUGs to open a path between here and MOHAI . They form together to create this liquid like wall, and she walks through. In the museum the same wall is formed, and she walks out the other side. The BUGs split up and scatter around the room.

Sani pulls his gun and tries to fire at a couple monsters on the wing, but fate had a different idea, he missed and shot a cable. The whole plane tilted, and everyone fell. Most where able to break their fall by throwing their bodies against the ground, but it was only temporary pain. Sasha quickly got back up to defend himself against the raging monsters and Trent starts look around the room for something he could use.

Trent finds a connection in the shadows and reaches through one into his Apartment and pulls out his giant mallet. He swings it towards another shadow and the mallet rips through there and appears in two other locations. One of the locations smashes the head of one of these creatures into a steal beam. The other location hits the creature square in the chess, but not before that creature picked up a saw blade from a display case and threw it.

The Blade cut through Trents pants and tore into his leg. Trent smells something. It is old, kind of like a wet carpet in an abandoned house. He looks around for the source and see something he can’t understand.

Two large creatures come blowing past and one snaps off the head of one of the humanoid monsters and the other rips another one of them in two. Sani grabs a third by the shirt and rolls back to kick another in-between the two new beasts.

These beasts are creatures that when standing are about 9 feet tall. They have wolf like features mixed with the incredible hulk. Just the sight of one invokes a flight response and everyone in the room had to consciously force themselves to stay put and see. It helps that Mages are mentally strong will beings, but Trent and Sani couldn’t even process what they were seeing and by morning, they may even forget what they saw and just remember something helped, but unless they actively try to remember what happened, their brains will try and protect them.

One of the humanoid creatures , the one with the top hat, makes a break for it. Trent swings his giant mallet through the shadow and barley nicks him as he attempts to make his exit, but not enough to stop him. When he pulls the mallet back the hat comes through the shadow and Trent goes to catch it and fumbles it to the ground. He can see that his hands a shaking violently. He realizes at that time his whole body is shaking and maybe he should run. They barely survived the other creatures now these gigantic beasts have arrived, they don’t stand a chance.

The creatures are Werewolves , but legion hasn’t gotten everything right about them. Vic knows the signs and knows they are in trouble. Violence is all these creatures know and they move faster than the forces he can conjure. Maybe he can get off a good hit to hopefully get some of these people out. Then he hears a whisper, can’t quite tell what it is, but the voice sounds familiar.

The Werewolves roar… well they try to. It was a battle cry, a powerful one that should have invoked a flight response and they would start the chase. These two wolves would have enjoyed a hunt through the urban streets of Seattle, ripped these intruders apart for coming onto their lands and bringing these creatures of the Wyrm. This place is protected, it is tied to the earth and it breads life, and these ignorant fools have come here to plague all of this. They need to die, their taste is addicting, to feel the heart beat one last time in-between those teeth will be worth it to our protector. Under the Luna sky their heads will roll. And they roared… Like it was said, they tried to. Nothing came out. They were silenced. The battle cry was interrupted by mute sounds, but the deafening scream was all that was muted.

“How?” one wolf thought to the other.

“I don’t understand it either brother.” The other said.

“They were fighting off eight of the plagued, maybe there is more to them.” The first one thought back.

“They are locks, we should tell them to just leave.” The other replied.

The first one’s body changed and unknown to the others this conversation happened at the speed of thought. He formed back into a more human like creature. Still very tall, still very scary, and said “Warlocks Leave, you have brought these creatures onto our scared Caern.”

“Wait, we were attacked, we didn’t let them…” Sasha starts to say.

“THIS IS NOT A NEGOTIATION!” the wolf man yells.

Trent fell into a shadow and popped out of there. He was not going to stick around for that aftermath, and fells super lucky to still be alive.

Outside they are standing around Vic ’s car, sirens can be heard in the distance. “Anyone need a ride?” Vic asks.

“Dah,” Sasha replies, “Thank you for showing up to help. How did you know?”

“Blame this guy,” Vic says.

“Fate has a way to bring us to where we need to be.” Sani says.

“So, you manipulate Fate?” Xenori says

“It is more like Fate guides me.” Sani replies

“How did you and the red head get here?” Sasha asks Xen.

“Oh Trent ?” Xen thinks for a moment, “I am not sure, he kind of just fell into place. I followed him.”

“Well, really.” Sasha begins, “Thank you. I am not sure I would have made it out of there.”

“You fucking pussy as bitch!” Trent says. The scene switches to Trent apartment and he is in the bathroom staring at himself in the mirror. The reflection can be seen that he is cleaning up a wound to his leg, all his sheets have been ripped off his bed, and there can be seen a little blood in them as well.

Trent forgot about his cut when he ported back to his place and he landed in his bed. “What the fuck are you doing.” He says, but now we can tell it is only the mirror version of him saying these things. Trent isn’t the one talking, but his reflection is. “A couple of dogs show up and you, a master wizard, freak the fuck out and run. Seriously, why do I waste my time with you?”

“Fuck you Puck!” Trent frustrated by falling into a battle with monsters and almost checking out of this world. “It isn’t like I was prepared for this!”

“What do you think we have been doing this whole time?” his reflection says

“Pranks!” Trent says reasonably. “That is all we do, we prank people, and try to make a couple peoples lives better. But everything is going to shit lately. I almost had a person land on me while committing suicide, I am being chased by some kind of Terminator, and now I just got into a cage fight with a bunch of vampire wannabes! How have you prepared me for this? Also, dogs?”

“Everything we have done together has prepared you for this. It is just now your time to act and you wuss out! I can’t believe you haven’t figured this out by now. Dogs! The fucking werewolves you moron.”

“What werewolves ?”

“Ugh, delirium has set in. you’re probably not remembering them again.”

“Look, what do you want me to do?” Trent resigns

“More.” Puck says just as the reflection returns to mirror Trent .

In the car driving under the Seattle night, traffic has seemed to clear up and it is easy cruising. Sani is no longer feeling the pull to go somewhere, and they all decide to go home to get some rest. Vic is driving them all.

“What were those things?” Xenori asks.

“Servant of Vampires .” Vic idly answers. “They are high on Vampire blood and will do whatever they must to get their next fix.”

“You seem to know a lot about these things.” Sasha points out.

“It is kind of my job as a hermetic mage. We spend years researching all sorts of things that exist in our world.” Vic replies.

“Wait… there are Vampires ?” Xen asks.

“Yes there are!” Sasha replies with a hint of anger “They do ‘fuck you’ things to your head.”

“Do you think we’re the only special ones on the planet right now?” Vic responds to answer her question with a question.

“Well, there are seven less tonight.” Xen answers.

“Those were just servants, like I mentioned, vampires would have been much worse, but lucky for us they don’t like to get their hands dirty if they can help it.”

“You two looked a little roughed up when you arrived, were you in a car accident or something?” Sasha just now remembers. “I can help.”

“It is ok.” Sani replies, “Hanging out with this guy” (pointing to Vic ) “comes with hazards. But we should be fine in a night or two.” Then he concentrates on hums to himself. Sasha can see the life energies flow through him. It is different than how Sasha manipulates it, but it is just as affective, but it defiantly created a ripple in reality.

They seem to get where they are going and Sasha is leaning into Vic window. “Here you go.” Vic says as he hands him a business card.

“You just give business cards to people you meet? American’s are weird.” Sasha says in reply. “But yeah, I’ll call you.” Then Vic drives off.

Trent answers the phone “What!”

“Everything ok?” Xen asks cautiously.

“Sorry, yeah, just… well you’re having the same night.” Trent says.

Xen nods, then realizes she is on the phone. “Yeah… I get it. Look, the others want to meet up tomorrow at this sandwich shop called. Piroshki’s on 3rd , you should join us.”

Trent thinks about it. ‘More’ he hears Puck cursing him out. “Yeah, I can be there.”

Game 01 | Home | 01 Game Notes | Game 04

Game 02

Overview

Real World Date: 08/17/2019

Game Notes

Cascade is an urban neighborhood abutting Downtown Seattle and to the east of Queen Anne District. They are usually lumped together. Historic structures in Cascade Neighborhood include St Spiridon's Orthodox Cathedral, Immanuel Lutheran Church, and several defunct laundry blocks. One such place in this district is Mary’s Place a center for to help women and children out of homelessness.

Sasha steps off the bus and walks in to do his weekly volunteering. He is greeted at the door by one of the young assistants that work there. “ Sasha , there is someone here looking for you back in Mary’s office.” Sasha confused, but decides to go check it out. People don’t normally look for him at these places.

When he steps into the room he is greeted by a person of power. This person is dressed in a suit and tie. They introduced themself, “Mr Laskin, welcome. I thought I would find you here. My name is Agent Blair , I work for the NWO and I thought you could help me on a case.”

Sasha takes a seat cautiously. Sasha has a history with the Technocracy , and it has never went well for him. This could be a trick. “Alright? What do you need?”

“I wish to talk about the … events that occurred at Trinity Nightclub the other night, during your… time-lapse?” Agent Blair says. She doesn’t have an accent, but she seems to have trouble with words. It is almost like she is new to the language. “Do you have any… recollection, or have you had any… memory flashes since the… event?”

“No, nothing.” Sasha answers.

Agent Blair looks excited, but she knows Sasha will most likely refuse. “We can help with that. I could abstract any memories that are being repressed.”

“That’s a big no.” Sasha replies before her sentence gets much passed the word ‘abstract’.

“I see.” They say with a little let down in their voice. “Then may I offer an alternative solution. Will you … retain employment with Trinity Nightclub ?”

“Planned on it.” He replies

While reaching into their bag, they pull out a small jar of some kind of ointment. “This is an ointment. It will… alleviate any mind control affects you may be… subject to. Just spread it over the eyes.” Blair looks from the cream to him “we want to catch this anomaly”

“What is it?” Sasha asks

Blair looks at him with confidence, “It is a leach. God I hate that word… Vampire you’d say.” She waits for a reaction and she wasn’t surprised when she saw the realization come across Sasha ’s face that he confronted a vampire. “You seem to have found yourself in a middle of a … turf war(?).”

“Between who and the Vampires?” Sasha asks. Agent Blair believes Sasha to have accepted reality and starts looking for solutions. They thing to themself that Sasha would make a good asset.

“Vampires” Blair replies “Like there are many Traditions and Technocrats, there are many Vampires and they don’t all agree. I need to know who this is so we can… overcome it”

“I will do this.” Sasha says grabbing the ointment.

Blair stands up and hands him a card, “Please call me once you know something. We are just interested in the vampire.”

The Nanobots or BUGs leave Susan’s room after a quick scan and quickly make their way back to Xenori , once they are back outside, she stands up and makes her way around the corner. Using the BUGs they surround Xenori and she programs a disguise. This disguise wouldn’t fool anyone if they took a close look, but it may be good enough to slip by the guard desk while they are dealing with Trent . She walks through the lobby and it works, she continues to head towards the elevator and presses the button to go up.

When Xenori reaches the door her nanobots come crawling down her arm, to her hand, and extend out to be inserted into the keyhole. A couple ticks and a click, the door opens. She goes into the room and her BUGs disperse as her disguise drops. She walks around the room where she can hear the laugh track of some show playing in the background. The room feels quiet, Xenori knows what waits her in the kitchen and when she gets in there, she analyzes the woman is about her age. Xenori carefully pulls out the chip from the phone and runs a routine to copy it over and use it on a virtual drive on her phone.

She looks around the house for anything else, but the apartment seems clean. She makes her way into the bathroom and clogs up the tub and turns on the water, hoping the overflow will alert someone to the apartment. She approaches the door and her last BUG lands on her outstretched hand and crawls up and into her sleeve. She opens the door and sees a familiar face standing in front of her.

The scene changes, it is just moments before down in the lobby. Xenori , disguised as Susan , gets on the elevator. Trent is talking to the guards trying to find out any information about Manel . “Any information you can share with me would be helpful. A family member, friend, any one I could talk with.”

“Aren’t you the guy that he almost… landed on?” one guard ask.

“Yeah, that was me.” Trent replies.

“His sister was hoping you would stop by. She wanted to reach out to you. Asked me to give you this if you came by again.” The guard opens up a drawer and pulls out a card with a phone number on it.

“How did she know about me?” Trent asks.

“You’re kind of famous, page 3 in The Stranger has an article on the event.” He says.

Trent thanks the guard and starts to make his way out the doors. When he steps into the vestibule, he can see out the doors leading to the street, Frank, Jerry… or something. Anyway, that guy that chased him from the bar. Some kind of bad ass agent (his real name is Agent Thomas , but Trent isn’t good with his name). “Shit.”

Trent goes back inside and heads towards the bathroom. In there he keeps an eye under the door to see where the Agent goes. Trent couldn’t make out much, but he could hear well enough. The man came into the lobby and Trent heard two thuds, loud steps of shoes against tile floors, the ding of the elevator, and then the motor of the lift ascending. Trent steps out of the bathroom to see the two guards asleep on the desk. “Time to go.”

When he got outside, he saw there was a vehicle and a person inside monitoring the building. He was pretty sure it was a lookout. These agents like to work in pairs. Trent quickly got himself into an alley and ran towards the line of shadow. Trent stepped across the threshold and from the hallway of his apartment into his kitchen. “What did he want?”

The elevator opens up and seen through the lends of what feels like a set of computer glasses, we see the hallway on the 4 th floor of the Highland Steps . It scans the hall and pixels settle on objects that are in the hallway, like plants, a ball, a bag, art on the wall, and room numbers. They concentrate on room 436. The camera switches places and see to whom the glasses belong. A tall man with a sturdy build dressed like an agent of some kind of secret service stands with fist clenched and quickly spins his head to the door. He stands there for a moment and tilts his head like he is listening. We see through his eyes again and a wave file popped up on his HUD. Text below it reads “Analyzing” then flashes over to “Water”. Then a warning pops up “Approaching”.

Xenori standing in front of the door. “Oh hi, I don’t think I will be needing anything you are…” He quick draws and shoots her. It only nicks her and takes out a BUG in the process. Xen fights back, and manages to disarm him, but this creature is too strong.

The scene changes and a younger version of Xenori wearing some cybernetic head gear moving her hands around like she is working with an interactive computer, is standing next to a person in a coat. He is wearing a name tag “ Main-io ”. They are watching a spar between two people. One male and one female. They are in sports gear, but not wearing any kind of padding. They are very physically fit individuals. They are moving lightning quick and when they connect the impact is louder than normal. One is picked up and thrown into a cement block wall and the wall shatters. When the lady stands back up without looking like she sustained any injuries is when Xenori realized they are more than human. “HIT Mark V, beyond the peek of human potential.” Main-io said while continuing to watch the spar.

“So they are like Terminators?” Xenori asked.

Main-io laughs “A lot like them, where do you think the certified door expert James Cameron got his ideas?”

Back in the apartment, a fist swings down and misses Xen, but smashes into the ground. The ground shakes, it stands up and uppercuts Xenori and she goes flying back. She twitches her fingers and all the BUGs come rushing to her. They form a pad to catch her in the air, it looks like a pool of water if it could float in a sheet above the ground. As Xen hits the BUGs she can here in the background dialing of a number like on a land line. Then the connection makes what sounds like a 90’s modem and she gets sucked into the BUGs.

As she is vanishing the HIT Mark Agent Thomas has jumped above her in preparation to punching her body through the floor. If he connected, she would surely be dead. But right before contact as if going down a drain, Xenori was gone.

Vic and Sani bust into a veterinarian’s office. “We need your help.” Sani demands.

“What kind of animal is it?” the vet request.

“Human?” Vic responds.

“Look. I am not that kind of doctor. I can’t help you. You have two too many legs” the vet tries to make a joke.

Sani looks around the office and sees this place isn’t getting the clientele it needs to survive. The biggest give away are the bills stacked up and he can see some of the letters have pick paper inside. “We have money and it isn’t a secret you need it.” Sani pulls out a wad of cash. “Do my friend a favor.”

The vet looks at the cash and thinks about it. After a moment he sighs “Fine. Get on the table in room 3.”

Xenori woke up in a field. It was developed to look like a wheat field. She could see where a city was located, but it would take her too much time to walk. She reached into her pocket and after a second of download she pulled out what looks like a little toy. Throwing it on the ground a bar popped up above it reading “Loading 1%”, the percentage grew from 1% to 100% in about 15 seconds. “At least the connection is good here.” Xenori thought.

She sticks her hands into her pockets and when she pulls them out, she is wearing rings on each finger. Grabbing her wrist, she pulls what seems to be a pad into view. Xenori knows she doesn’t need to do all this as this isn’t real, but it is so much harder to do this without physical representation. She sets a destination and hops on the bike. Swinging her other arm down a pair of glasses form and she puts them on her face. If this were the real world, Xenori would have died when the bike took off. It went from 0 to 1,000 MPH almost instantly. Since this is the Digital Web , she was safe as this is the way people travel. Her bike is coded in such a way that as long as she is not in a developed space where crashing matters, she can just go whatever speed the server allows.

On her way, her system intercepts a message. It looks like a person named Trent is calling a person named Violet. She hears the message and Trent is leaving a voicemail, “I stopped by Highland Steps today and the guard gave me your number. He said you wanted to hear from me. My name is Trent , the paper got it wrong. Anyway, call me back”

Trent ’s phone rings with the ID as Unknown across the top. “Hello?” Trent answers.

“Can we talk?” Xen responds while flying through the biggest field she has ever ridden in.

Trent thinks for a second, “Violet?”

“No. We meet a while back; I was on a bike you were running from an Agent.” Xen tries to make Trent remember. She is also pausing while her system is running. It is tracking the call. It seems like wherever he is, there must be decent security, but at least she doesn’t have to fight it.

“OH! Frank! I remember you. I don’t think I ever got your name.”

“ Xenori . But his name was Thomas. Anyway, can we talk?” she asked again.

“I mean I guess that is what AHHHH” Trent pulls the phone away from him as he hears this loud dial tone and static. Then he hears a knock on the front door.

Outside Trent ’s apartment the speaker box makes a static sound and bust with what kind of looks like what static on an old television looks like until it forms a shape that looks like Xenori . It feels weird going from one world to another. She shivers, knocks, and then hears a bag full of groceries hit the floor.

She looks over and there is an older gentleman standing there with his mouth open, he was holding two bags of groceries, but now only one bag is in his arms.

Trent opens the door. “How the hell…”

“Can I come in?” Xen says as she walks into the apartment before the person outside can figure out how his jaw works to ask any questions.

Trent kind of surprised by this, closes the door, and tries again “How the hell…”

Xen says “You know that agent that was trying to kill you? They are called Hit marks, it is kind of like a terminator. I mean… like from Terminator 1, I guess you can include 2, but he is not a good guy.”

Trent processing this. Looks over at his door view screen and sees the grocery man from earlier walking down and looking in towards his apartment. Trent thought he just pissed off some dude in a suit. Nothing out of the ordinary. But someone actually trying to kill him, and he is a… “Wait like he is a Cyborg? Shit, stop distracting me, how the hell…”

“Yes. They are called Hit Marks. He was at the Highland Steps today. I thought it was weird that so were you.” She says

“…Find me” Trent finishes his sentence anyway.

Xen realizes she hasn’t really let Trent speak and decides to answer his question while processing her next thought. “Your phone is easily traceable. I have been shot and do you have anything to drink?”

Trent pulls out some Jägermeister, sees Xen’s face, put’s it away, and pulls out Vodka questionably. When he sees approval, he pours a glass with ice and then goes to get supplies.

When he comes back, he washes and treats her wound. She was luckily that she was only grazed so it was something Trent could handle. While he is treating her injury Xen tells him more about Thomas and that he works for an organization that is pretty powerful and warns him to be careful.

“Why does he want me?” Trent asks

Xenori ’s phone rings. The screen reads that it is in virtual phone mode and loaded as Susan ’s phone. “Hello?” she answers.

Trent wondering if she even realizes that he is still there says to no one in particular “Fuck, it wasn’t like we were having a conversation or anything.”

Xenori looks up from the phone “Can you get me some ice?”

Vic responds on the other side “Ice? Wait, who is this?”

“This is Susan ’s phone.” Xen responds

“I know that, where is Susan ?” Vic asks.

“Sorry, she lost it I am trying to get it back to her.” Xen says. She starts to tap into Vic ’s phone. When she looks at the screen she is suddenly seeing in waves. Xen can feel reality hitting her for her earlier jump. The digital web is dangerous to visit personally, and she is now paying for it. Sometimes you come back still partially connected.

“Look just take it to Highland Steps Apartments I will let the front desk know you’re coming.” Vic says hearing her go kind of absent.

“Yeah… I’ll do that.” Xen replies mechanically. She was still trying to figure out what she was seeing, hearing, feeling.

Vic hangs up and parks his car. On his way up to his penthouse he calls Highland Steps to let them know. When he calls, they tell him he needs to call Officer Ev. Vic asks why, but they wouldn’t say. He calls the officer and she informs him that Susan has died and they have some questions. “Could you come by my office tomorrow morning?” Vic agrees, but he can hear the tone that she has some questions and he may be on the suspect list.

Vic went into the apartment and Suni made himself comfortable in the living room. While Vic was in the shower Suni heard something at the front door. He went to look and saw what looked like a heat wave through the eyehole. The was a sigh and then he heard something towards Vic ’s room. Suni stealthily made his way down the hall, when a large beast jumped out at him. “Damnit Coyote” Suni said as he also heard what sounded like the shampoo bottle drop in the shower.

Suni smiled and shook his head, he knows this trick. Entropy is causing their conversation to be silent. Coyote wasn’t smiling. He was in his beast form and he looked angry. “It hurt us. What are you going to do about it?” he said to Suni, then lunged at him. They scuffled a little and some music kicked on.

Vic thought he heard something, but then could hear the rhythm of a beat and knew it had to be his whole house sound system. As they fought around the living room. Things would fall over, but coyote was smooth knocking everything perfectly back into place. Suni fought hard to keep up with him, but they have done this dance before. “I don’t know what to do.” Suni finally said.

“Go back to where it attacked us.” Coyote said. “Go back, find the corruption, and we will kill it.” Suni heard the music turn down and he turned to see Vic at one of the wall controls. He looks back at the room, but Coyote was gone, and it was almost as if he was never there.

Vic hands Suni a package. “I need you to put this in a safety deposit box.” The item he handed him was wrapped up tightly.

Suni could feel the power coming from the diadem “what is this?”

“It is a very powerful item. Do not touch it, and for the love of God, do not put it on.” Vic warns.

“Yeah. Got it.” Suni says.

After dropping off the item Suni takes Vic to the location where the school bus was located. Suni tells Vic “I need to see what happened here. There was a school bus which is all I can really remember. I am not sure if it was something around the bus, in the bus, but it hit me hard.”

They were standing on the corner where Suni remembers it happening. Vic saw a car slowdown and look over in their direction. He could see a tattoo of an eight ball on a person neck. “Fuck, we have a problem.” Before they could get far, the four caught up and attacked.

Suni tried to start talking them out of it, and where he had one guy lower his knife, the other guy didn’t have a problem punching a man well into his 50s.

Vic started tagging different things he saw on the street. Vic carries these stickers that have pentacles with circles on them. They are a cheap way to allow him to connect his raw power to things. It gives him the focus he needs to control the chaos around him. It goes off perfectly. A power transformer blows and a cable drops throwing sparks all over the place. Multiple car alarms went off, a crash happened in the intersection, streetlights all became green, walk signs all said go and you could hear the visual impairment assistance “Walk… Walk… Walk…” This caused a great enough distraction that allowed Vic to start his escape.

BANG BANG! One of the four let off his gun but Vic just dove around the corner. The other guy with the knife went to stab Suni but didn’t see how close he was to the base of the tree. Around this tree in Seattle someone placed a small wrought iron fence around it to assist people into going around and not stepping on the bed. His foot got caught in it, and the spike went through his leg. The gang member screamed and Suni ran… right into the man with the gun.

They both stumbled and regained their balance. As Suni turned the corner the gunman released another BANG and Suni felt a sharp pain in his leg.

Vic was a little angry and a little worried, Suni was hobbling and wasn’t going to make it to the car.  He dropped to the ground and drew a circle around him. He dabbed a tiny piece of blood and could feel the circle pop. He started a low chant and focused on the gun. He knew this gun. He could feel the cold metal, the weight, his senses connected him to the chamber, and he muttered the right words, with the right will, and the right focus that would convert kinetic energy into thermodynamics. The gun went to bark one more time, but exploded instead, ripping apart the wielder’s fingers.

Suni fell into the car and Vic peeled away, “What was the name of that Vet? Teddy?” Suni says as they see a dump truck veer off the road to avoid another car and narrowly missed the shooter before crashing into a Subway.

//Cut Scene//

A man in a million-dollar suit wearing a purple tie is sitting on his desk talking to another person when he hears the cries of someone heading towards the room. They come through the door and he sees a man with his fingers blown off. “What Happened?”

While they were telling him, the gunman couldn’t get his sobbing under control so the man with the purple tie shot him. “Continue.” His men did but was frightened. “So, what you’re saying is you hunted down the guy that shot my brother, and when you tried to take him out, our guns… our very expensive, high demand guns… failed? If our buys hear about this incompetence, we could lose a lot more than money.”

The man that was holding the other man whose fingers were blown off stood up and handed him a piece of a sticker. The man in the expensive suit looks over at one similar to it on his desk. “What’s going on here?”

//End Cut Scene//

“Life is chalk fucking full of people trying to influence you. The absence of it, while odd, is much preferable.” Sasha thought to himself while walking down the street heading to Trinity Nightclub . He put on the ointment that Agent Blair gave him, and the results were… strange. Sasha never really thought about advertisements being consider manipulation before, but the ointment did. Store front signs, billboards, or stickers on the sides of busses didn’t grab his attention, it was almost as if they were never there.

While standing outside the club a man dressed well, but not quite of this time came up to him and offered him a smoke. Sasha turned it down. “Oh right, your body is a temple.” (Link to the Unknown Vampire for reference)

“Who are you?” Sasha asks.

“I should be going; you don’t seem as fun tonight as usual. You can forget now.” He says as he starts walking inside.

“Whoa, excuse me buddy.” Sasha says and seems to catch the man by surprise. “I don’t recognize you, what do you mean don’t seem as fun?”

The man slowly turns back to Sasha , he chuckles and says “I love watching your parkour. You are entertaining to talk to, but alas, I must be off. You may forget now.”

“What’s your name? Were you hear the other night?” Sasha inquires.

Which a blur of motion the man was standing behind Sasha “Something is different about you. Something smells different. Why do I not affect you?”

Sasha turns around to face him and he blurs back a step. “Don’t know, but I am not getting a good feeling about you. What is your name?”

“I’ll come back another night. We can talk again.” He says as he walks away.

Game 00 | Home | 01 Game Notes | Game 08

Fronts

Game Overview

Theme: Consensual Reality is Changing - Due to so many people subscribing to the belief of the Fake News, Flat Earthers, not believing in Climate Science, Vaccines cause autism, Holocaust never happened, and even more real things that have no grounding in reality, this is changing the Consensual Reality and causing glitches in magick. Sometimes Paradox happens with Coincidental Effects, but sometimes it doesn’t happen with Vulgar Effects. It is hard to predict, and the bubbles of shifting reality do not stay in one place for long. No one knows why this is happening in Seattle or how many other places it is happening.

Threat: The Technocracy are Relentless – Most places the Technocracy has been laying low and not bothering the Traditions for many years, but in recent years the Technocracy hasn’t been going out of their way to take out Reality Deviants, but when one “gets in their way” they have no problem removing the delinquent. The rise in attacks seems to not be officially sanctioned. The contacts within the Technocracy claim to know nothing about it and deny their involvement with the accused. Unfortunately, there isn’t a truce when mages give cause for other groups to attack, such as thievery, assault, divulging secrets, and more.

Keep in mind, with the Fronts below that some of them should be combined, and some of them only partially link up. As we continue this list will keep getting additional information added to it until the Front is completed.

Front 1

F1 - Title: The Breath-Taking Court Case

F1 - Description: There was a court case where a rich teenager by the name of Ethan Brewster, was driving under the influence. He crashed his car accidently killing a person by the name of Jakki Davis. In the last few weeks there has been a number of deaths by asphyxiation. It turns out, that the deaths are all members of the court case, all but 3.

Vic was looking into some possible magickal items for Susan. He found one at a pawn shop ran by a gang member named Dee. Vic retrieved the item, but Susan died also by asphyxiation. It wasn’t until later that she was connected to the court case.

Trent was walking down the street when a younger adult named Manel fell and almost landed on him. Since his apartment is right above Susan’s apartment, it is believed that these cases may be connected.

There was also an incident where the apartment right beneath Susan’s the tenant was taken to the hospital due to breathing issues.

* Manel falling, Dee Shooting, and the Magicakal Items are split into different Fronts below

F1 - Faces and Places: Jakki (unseen)

Susan

Garry Davis

Manel

From Court:

Diana Tera - Judge

Peter Reed – M – 20 – A

Paula Cox – F – 41 – D

Robert Gonzalez – M – 25 – D

Christine Gonzales – F – 25 – D

Jean Johnson – F – 70 – A

Deborah Moore – F – 29 – D

Joshua Taylor – M – 39 – A

Jason Richardson – M – 35 – D

Sarah Wilson – F – 29 – D

Nicholas Murphy – M – 71 – D

Susan Flores – F – 35 – D (from above)

Theresa Diaz – F – 59 – D

Front 2

F2 - Title: Vampire Turf War

F2 - Description: At Trinity Nightclub there has been a death. A person not yet 21 by the name of Bernard, died of exsanguination, but “officially” of a drug overdose. This started a war between two faction of Vampires and it is going to get worse. Agent Blair, an agent within one of the divisions of the Technocracy, offered aid to help bring the killer to justice.

Front 3

F3 - Title: The Clog in the Wheel

F3 - Description: There was a ritual that the Euthanitoi performed to show them the one who is clogging fate. With this person around there is an entropy bubble hovering over the city and once popped, no one knows what will happen. This is so powerful that it caused an Oracle to return to the chantry to aid. What was shown was a child. An elementary school girl. But Seattle is a big place and the Chantry doesn’t know where to find her, but Sani does. Now he has to make a choice.

F3 - Faces and Places: The Girl

F3 - Events: Euthanitoi Chantry : Performed ritual

Front 4

F4 - Title: Girl at Seattle U

F4 - Description: A girl disappears in her dorm. Trent investigates on where she vanished to. On investigation she appeared and pulled him somewhere else.

F4 - Faces and Places: Ella Hearts

F4 - Events: Trent goes to her dorm

Front 5

F5 - Title: Dyron , the lil brother of Dee

F5 - Description: Dyron was stuck in a gang called Duces 8. He had little options and these were the lest worst of all the options. Dyron’s brother Dee used to roll with D8, and decided to take over when he found out his little brother was in trouble.  He did what he had to do. He also came to own a pawn shop. He used the pawn shop as a front and did business with the locals of Central District.

Dee came into an item and became possessed by it. Dee was killed by a man named Vic when he started to threaten him and people he cares about.

Dee showed up as a ghost to Vic, he was worried his little brother was going to be killed by his Step Brother Tyrone (Ty). Vic said he would help get Dyson to his Uncle Owen.

Seemingly Unrelated Xenori was looking into the homeless getting stabbed. She chased a lead into an abandoned building and was captured by thousands of spiders.

When she woke up she was at Gas Works Park with a homeless teenager named Dyron. She couldn’t see and Dyron helped her escape, but not before they were attacked by a werespider (aka Ananasi or Spider Lady).

F5 - Faces and Places: Dyron

Dee

Tyrone

Uncle Owen (yeah I know how that sounds, I honestly only realized on 01/07/2020)

Front 6

F6 - Title: Survivors Guilt

* This Front is connected to “The Breath-Taking Court Case”

F6 - Description: Trent was walking down the street when a body almost fell on him. He barely got out of the way in time. Unable to shake this scene Trent looked into who the person was and found his name to be Manel. Reaching out for family Trent found that he had a sister, Violet, attending college at Washington University.

After visiting with her Violet was convinced that Manel was not suicidal, but his death is being reported as such.

Violet has a boyfriend, but he gives a funny vibe to Trent and Xenori. A quick background check found him to be clean.

F6 - Faces and Places: Violet

Larry

Manel

University of Washington

Ugly Mug Cafe

Front 7

F7 - Title: Items of Seattle

F7 - Description: Susan was looking for lost items that she believes have found their way into Seattle. She has tracked down a Diadem. This was worn by Ancient Female Egyptian Warriors who were buried with royalty to protect them. She tracked it down and it is currently at a Pawn Shop, but the owner isn’t selling.

Vic took it from the owner, but it is not widely known that he is in possession of it.

The items missing are Bracelets, Belt, and Rings (two of them)

Storyteller Planning

Prev | Home | 00 Game Overview | The Party Sheet